(Sheldon:)She's still on probation, of course,
but I like her.
(Alicia:)Cool T-shirt.
(Penny:)Oh, yeah, I don't usually dress like this.
I'm going jogging.
- You don't jog.
- I can start.
(Sheldon:)The more likely explanation for your attire
is that you're out of clean clothes again.
- Thank you, Sheldon.
- You're welcome, Penny.
(Alicia:)Please, you look cute.
I'm dressed like a slob today too.
Oh, ha, ha.
LEONARD:
I think you look fantastic.
- This one's a player, huh?
- Oh, yeah, be careful.
- Thanks for the warning.
- Okay.
- I'll see you around.
- See you.
[KEYS JINGLING]
[IN MOCKING VOICE]
"I'm dressed like a slob today too."
(Sheldon:)Oh, mimicry.
(Sheldon:)I enjoy mimicry.
(Sheldon:)I've been working on Admiral Ackbar
from Return of the Jedi.
[LOUDLY]
It's a trap.
(Sheldon:)You have to imagine me
with a giant squid head.